<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Spicer Matthews Personal Site</title>
    <link>https://spicermatthews.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Spicer Matthews Personal Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 12:18:58 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://spicermatthews.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Spicer&#39;s Rules on How and When To Test Your Code</title>
      <link>https://spicermatthews.com/blog/spicers-rules-on-how-and-when-to-test-your-code-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 12:18:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spicermatthews.com/blog/spicers-rules-on-how-and-when-to-test-your-code-/</guid>
      <description>I just marked my 20th year as a professional software developer - meaning I received my first paycheck for writing code 20 years ago. I have to admit it has been a wild ride of successes, failures, crazy ideas, and immense learning. Throughout this journey, the topic of unit tests, or any kind of testing for that matter, has always been front and center for me. This topic has led countless barroom debates and even more IRC fights - yep, showing my age here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Hugo with Google Docs</title>
      <link>https://spicermatthews.com/blog/using-hugo-with-google-docs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 12:18:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spicermatthews.com/blog/using-hugo-with-google-docs/</guid>
      <description>Quick tip alert! This is how I import Google docs into Hugo. I am becoming a big fan of Hugo to build static sites like this one and this one. Since Hugo does not ship with any fancy GUI as other content management systems do -- typically you produce your content within your text editor such as Atom.
 Text editors are great but they are not ideal for producing well-thought-out written content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delighting Customers With Airbnb</title>
      <link>https://spicermatthews.com/blog/delighting-customers-with-airbnb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 12:18:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spicermatthews.com/blog/delighting-customers-with-airbnb/</guid>
      <description>This week, we launched bendmountbachelorvillage.com for really no good reason. For years now, we have been using Airbnb to rent out our vacation rental in Bend, OR. The truth is, we designed this website back in 2012 when we were using Craigslist to find nightly renters. Before we had time to launch the site, Airbnb became a thing and changed our rental business in the best possible ways. This past weekend I decided I was sick of looking at this linger todo and I launched the site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World: My New Blog, Hugo, Tailwind CSS, and More</title>
      <link>https://spicermatthews.com/blog/hello-world-my-new-blog-hugo-tailwind-css-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 19:02:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spicermatthews.com/blog/hello-world-my-new-blog-hugo-tailwind-css-and-more/</guid>
      <description>Today, I am launching, once again, my personal blog. Starting over. Hopefully, this is my last reboot (more on that below). I could not even begin to count the number of blogs I have had in my life. Currently, I blog for Options Cafe, Skyclerk, and Cloudmanic. However, in the past, I have had all sorts of personal blogs. Just for fun here are some of my past blogs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>